[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was daredevil performer Steve-O from Jackass: The Movie born?", "correct_answer": "Wimbledon, London", "incorrect_answers": ["Los Angeles, California", "Conway, Arkansas", "Ontario, Canada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors did not appear in the 1988 baseball movie Bull Durham?", "correct_answer": "Bruce Willis", "incorrect_answers": ["Kevin Costner", "Tim Robbins", "Susan Sarandon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who built the first restaurant from the McDonalds chain, one of the worlds largest chains of fast-food restaurants?", "correct_answer": "The MacDonald brothers", "incorrect_answers": ["The U. S. meatpackers conglomerate", "Ray Kroc", "Dave Thomas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What rock musicians real name is Gordon Matthew Thomas Sumner?", "correct_answer": "Stings", "incorrect_answers": ["Bonos", "Kid Rocks", "Dave Matthews"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call the type of ants that plant seeds to grow food?", "correct_answer": "Harvester ants", "incorrect_answers": ["Formicadae", "Thresher ants", "Farmer ants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The representatives of this dog breed are small, have long white silky fur and are also known as Roman Ladies Dogs.", "correct_answer": "Maltese", "incorrect_answers": ["Norrbottenspets", "Phalene", "Mudi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the movie Clueless released in theaters?", "correct_answer": "1995", "incorrect_answers": ["1993", "1994", "1996"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Back to the Future, Martys actions in 1955 change the name of the mall where he and Doc meet in 1985, to secretly  test the time machine.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who had Solomons wisdom, Hercules strength, Atlas stamina, Zeus power, Achilles courage, and Mercurys speed?", "correct_answer": "Captain Marvel", "incorrect_answers": ["Captain America", "The Hulk", "Superman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color was the aardvark from the Pink Panther cartoon?", "correct_answer": "Blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Red", "Pink", "Gray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Potophobia is the abnormal fear of what?", "correct_answer": "alcohol", "incorrect_answers": ["potatoes", "ibuprofen", "church"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "George Crum invented potato chips.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]